db = client['IdiotKnowledge']
collection = db['gamequestion']
    {
        question: "When did we start using Schampoo for the first time?",
        correct_answer: "The 1930s",
        incorrect_answers: ["The 1760s", "The 1880s", "2800 BC"],

    },
    {
        question: "How many people in the world share the same birth day as you?",
        incorrect_answers: ["Around 8 Thousand", "No one", "Around 50 Million"],
        answer: "Around 19 Million"
    },
    {
        question: "What book, published 1966, has been printed in roughly as many editions as the bible throughout the ages?",
        incorrect_answers: ["The Magic Finger, by Roald Dahl", "Tai Pan, by James Clavell", "Heroes, Gods and Monsters of the Greek Myths, by Bernard Evslin"],
        answer: "Quotations from Chairman Mao Zedong, by Mao Zedong"
    },
    {
        question: "In which country are the most people executed each year?",
        incorrect_answers: ["The United States of America", "Arabia", "Russia"],
        answer: "China"
    },
    {
        question: "At what time of day do most elderly people die?",
        incorrect_answers: ["In the afternoon", "In the evening", "At night"],
        answer: "In the morning"
    },
    {
        question: "Why are brown eggs more expensive than white eggs?",
        incorrect_answers: ["Brown hens are rarer and therefore more expensive than white hens", "There is no difference between brown and white eggs", "Brown eggs are more durable than white eggs"],
        answer: "Hens nesting brown eggs are bigger and more expensive to raise"
    },
    {
        question: "Roughly what percentage of all books published are loss-making ventures?",
        incorrect_answers: ["Around 100%", "Around 54%", "Around 25%"],
        answer: "Around 80%"
    },
    {
        question: "Would you be able to surgically replace your eyes and be able to use them?",
        incorrect_answers: ["Yes, but there would be risks of your brain become aware of the new eyes", "No, the connection can't be manually recreated", "No, because eyes are uniquely wired from person to person"],
        answer: "Yes, there would be little to no risk"
    },
    {
        question: "A lot of people recognize the smell of leather. But what exactly is the source of that smell?",
        incorrect_answers: ["The cowhide", "Smoke from the tanning process", "Oil used to soften the leather"],
        answer: "Materials used in the bleaching process"
    },
    {
        question: "An american police officer will say “You have the right to remain silent. Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law” when arresting somebody. What does a Swedish police officer say in the same situation?",
        "choice1": "The swedish equivalent of the same phrase",
        "choice2": "“Nu åker du in i häktet”",
        "choice3": "They say nothing",
        "choice4": "They laugh at you",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Why do snakes shed their skin?",
        "choice1": "Because they grow, but the skin doesn't",
        "choice2": "Because the skin stiffens and becomes harder to move around in",
        "choice3": "Because they need to repair",
        "choice4": "Because the skin is a nutricious snack to distract other predators",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "In how many Km/h does the world's fastest elevator travel in?",
        "choice1": "Around 40 Km/h",
        "choice2": "Around 88 Km/h",
        "choice3": "Around 100 Km/h",
        "choice4": "Around 60 Km/h",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Can an astronaut call home to Earth with a cellphone while in outer space?",
        "choice1": "Yes, with the right provider",
        "choice2": "No, there'd be too much interference",
        "choice3": "Yes, but with constant breaking audio breakup",
        "choice4": "No, cellphones do not work in outer space",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "On which weekday are most bank robberies commited?",
        "choice1": "Monday",
        "choice2": "Saturday",
        "choice3": "Wednesday",
        "choice4": "Friday",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How long does it take to record 5 minutes of action for a feature film?",
        "choice1": "A day",
        "choice2": "5 minutes",
        "choice3": "10 minutes",
        "choice4": "1 Hour",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many of the almost 7 billion people on Earth have never seen snow?",
        "choice1": "Roughly 6 Billion",
        "choice2": "Roughly 2 Billion",
        "choice3": "Roughly 4 Billion",
        "choice4": "Roughly 1 Billion",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What food can you store for several hundred years without it going bad?",
        "choice1": "Bread",
        "choice2": "Grapes",
        "choice3": "Jelly",
        "choice4": "Honey",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How old is the oldest known pornographic film?",
        "choice1": "From around 1800s",
        "choice2": "From around 1900s",
        "choice3": "From around 1950s",
        "choice4": "From around 1850s",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "According to research, how much time of their lives do men spend in total spying on women?",
        "choice1": "Half their life",
        "choice2": "20 Years",
        "choice3": "1 Year",
        "choice4": "13 Years",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Do you hear better or worse when your stomach is full?",
        "choice1": "You hear better",
        "choice2": "You hear worse",
        "choice3": "There is no difference",
        "choice4": "It varies from person to person",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Police officers will often say “We've got a 10-71” in American movies. What does this code mean?",
        "choice1": "A Shooting",
        "choice2": "A Murder",
        "choice3": "A Bomb threat",
        "choice4": "Nothing",
        answer: 1
    }
];
